playtomic.com 2015-02-23

# Privacy policy | Playtomic

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.

By using our web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

For the analytics side of things we do not track information that identifies you personally. What we track and analyse is total aggregate data for events such as views, plays or other events where your activities are counted and added to the totals. At its simplest, when you play a game, that game's "play" counter goes up 1.

Leaderboards and saving levels you make in level editors may require you to provide a name which may or may not be linked to your identify by 3rd party services (eg gamersafe username, mochicoins username, or a name you just enter). On Facebook your name and Facebook user id may be recorded with your score or level.

When you visit our web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregrate basis as you and others browse our Web Site.

## Registration Information

You will provide us information about yourself, your firm or company and your practises when you register to be a member of Playtomic, register for certain services or register for email newsletters and alerts. You may also provide additional comments on how you see Playtomic servicing your needs and interests.

## Email Information

If you choose to correspond with us through email we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

## Sharing Information with Third Parties

We do not share your information with any third parties unless required to by law, court order, or our discretion with respect to law enforcement agencies.
